A Guide to the Charles Olson Research Collection 1969.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Works, undated, 1927-1969
  - E. Unpublished poems
    - In the octave, the octave of the birth of... Typescript. 1p., January 8, 1951. (Box 21, Folder 936)
    - Burned. Carbon copy. 7p., June 30, 1951. (Box 21, Folder 937)
    - Three Persons, by Persiflage. Typescript. 3p., September 17, 1952. (Box 21, Folder 938)
    - Words are wonders and their laws... Typescript/Photocopy. 2p., ca. 1951-1955. (Box 21, Folder 939)
    - 1953-1960 (Box 22)
    - To Be Thrown to the Wind Immediately After... Typescript. 2p., ca. 1953. (Box 22, Folder 940)
    - Her Version. Typescript. 1p., ca. 1953. (Box 22, Folder 941)
    - It Isn't True. Typescript. 2p., ca. 1953. (Box 22, Folder 942)
    - A Palinode (No. 22). Typescript. 4p., ca. May 1953. (Box 22, Folder 943)
    - Blackball. Typescript. 1p., May 1953. (Box 22, Folder 944)
    - For John Keats. Manuscript/Typescript. 5p., ca. July 1953. (Box 22, Folder 945)
    - The Knife. Typescript. 1p., July 12, 1953. (Box 22, Folder 946)
    - To a Man who is the Best Goddamn Painter in America... Typescript. 1p., ca. July 21, 1953. (Box 22, Folder 947)
    - Palms and Stars. Typescript. 1p., November 3-4, 1953. (Box 22, Folder 948)
    - Night's waters where he fears to dive... Typescript. 1p., ca. 1953. (Box 22, Folder 949)
    - Credo in Unam. Typescript. 9p., July 11, 1954. (Box 22, Folder 950)
    - Beginning at the Beginning. Typescript. 3p., ca. 1954. (Box 22, Folder 951)
    - One night, in a restaurant near you people... Manuscript. 1p., January 1954. (Box 22, Folder 952)
    - Blowing his horn. Typescript. 2p., May 31, 1954. (Box 22, Folder 953)
    - The Journey. Typescript. 2p., ca. 1955-1957. (Box 22, Folder 954)
    - On Duncan On The Pantokrator... Typescript. 12p., ca. August 20, 1955. (Box 22, Folder 955)
    - The World We Carve Our Lives Out of the Middle of. Manuscript. 1p., ca. January 15, 1957. (Box 22, Folder 956)
    - Backward it compells Gloucester... Manuscript. 1p. Written on "Delta Poetry Magazine, October 1957"., ca. October 1957. (Box 22, Folder 957)
    - Figures on the Landscape. Typescript. 2p., ca. 1957-1959. (Box 22, Folder 958)
    - Release me from the bonds of love... Manuscript. 2p., ca. 1957-1962. (Box 22, Folder 959)
    - Sit in the water, on the Mediterranean green slime... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1958-1963. (Box 22, Folder 960)
    - The Golden Flower. Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., ca. 1958. (Box 22, Folder 961)
    - Firstness/Lastness. Manuscript. 1p., 1958. (Box 22, Folder 962)
    - The Snow 2. Typescript. 1p., ca. November 1958 - March 1963. (Box 22, Folder 963)
    - A Commonplace. Manuscript/Typescript. 4p., January 1958. (Box 22, Folder 964)
    - Do you see how deep the well is... Typescript. 1p., January 1958. (Box 22, Folder 965)
    - Etc. Typescript. 1p., ca. 1957-1958. (Box 22, Folder 966)
    - As cats who come in the night... Manuscript/Typescript. 9p., ca. Spring 1958 - Spring 1963. (Box 22, Folder 967)
    - Frederic Mistral... Manuscript. 1p., ca. April 7, 1958. (Box 22, Folder 968)
    - Chief of the Westerners. Photocopy. 1p., ca. 1959. (Box 22, Folder 969)
    - Too much wind outside... Photocopy. 1p., ca. 1959. (Box 22, Folder 970)
    - An Ocean Race. Photocopy. 1p., ca. 1959. (Box 22, Folder 971)
    - A new moon... Photocopy. 2p. From notebook "1959". (Box 22, Folder 972)
    - Art is an imitation of the cosmos, we are divided in purpose between God and Nature - a soliloquy out loud. Typescript. 2p., 1959. (Box 22, Folder 973)
    - Working Conclusion. Typescript. 3p., 1959. (Box 22, Folder 974)
    - One way to draw together the hole in the skein... Typescript. 1p., January 12, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 975)
    - January, 1959. Manuscript/Typescript. 4p., January 28, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 976)
    - While the dream of giving over to the Earth's greatness... Manuscript. 5p. Also see the following letters (separated from the manuscript): 1) dated April 8, 1959, from Richard P. Weinart, Civil War Branch, The National Archives, to CO; 2) dated April 10, 1959, from Herman R. Friis, Cheif Archivist, Cartographic Records Division, The National Archives, to CO; 3) dated May 13, 1959, from Victor Gondos, Jr., Archivist in Charge, Civil War Branch, The National Archives, to CO; and 4) dated May 27, 1959, from Victor Gondos to CO., April - May 1959. (Box 22, Folder 977)
    - Vs. Babson. Manuscript. 1p., ca. April 5, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 978)
    - Southmead (where Pearce was)... Photocopy. 1p. From notebook "II May 1959"., ca. May 18, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 979)
    - Throw the pigeon up... Typescript/Photocopy. 2p. See notebook "1959/Feb 13th on.", June 29, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 980)
    - Dogtown is the humid nature... Photocopy. 1p., November 16, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 981)
    - Looking over the ground... Photocopy. 1p., November 18, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 982)
    - Another Amuletic Song. Typescript/Photocopy. 3p., November 24-25, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 983)
    - The pasture is so rich... Photocopy. 1p., ca. November 28, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 984)
    - Ocean, or the Travels of Maximus. Photocopy. 1p., November 28, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 985)
    - An excursion to New Jersey... Photocopy. 1p., November 30, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 986)
    - A Pretty Serious Poem. Photocopy. 1p., December 1, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 987)
    - Alone in this kitchen... Photocopy. 1p., December 2, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 988)
    - Eurybia white sea... Photocopy. 1p., December 4, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 989)
    - The Sun hides Moon's Pieces in a hollow log... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., December 9, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 990)
    - Fragments of Heraclitus. Photocopy. 3p., November 19, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 991)
    - Ammonius says Existence is Solely God's Life... Typescript/Photocopy. 4p., December 9, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 992)
    - Poem ["ever-lurking night is Bull-shit..."]. Photocopy. 1p., December 10, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 993)
    - So as to make the earth part of a circuit. Photocopy. 2p., December 10, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 994)
    - Congruence. Photocopy. 2p., December 11, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 995)
    - For RC. Photocopy. 2p., December 13, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 996)
    - to the Head of the Tide... Manuscript. 1p. Written on letter dated December 5, 1959, from Michael Shayer to CO., December 13, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 997)
    - Jack's a cat's cradle... Typescript/Photocopy. 2p., December 14, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 998)
    - A Hymn to the Bowels. Typescript/Photocopy. 2p., December 17, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 999)
    - The third one, who encircles, Amphitrite... Photocopy. 2p., December 21, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 1000)
    - I am Born. Typescript/Photocopy. 2p., December 21, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 1001)
    - Possibility that the one mystery proper is that one that anyone of us 'happens' at all?? Photocopy. 1p., December 23, 1959. (Box 22, Folder 1002)
    - Exe-gesis. Typescript. 1p. (Box 22, Folder 1003)
    - Of many a brave unbodied scheme... Photocopy. 1p., ca. 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1004)
    - My wild goose I'll play swan... Photocopy. 1p., ca. 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1005)
    - The 39 Propositions of Mexico. Photocopy. 1p., 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1006)
    - Wow, Hope, When Spring. Typescript/Photocopy. 3p., 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1007)
    - Sanchunyaton. Photocopy. 1p., 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1008)
    - In the Face of the Years to Place a Goat of Shell... Typescript/Photocopy. 2p., January 15, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1009)
    - Sanchuniathon. Photocopy. 1p., January 24, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1010)
    - Mistress Employment. Typescript. 2p., ca. February 9, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1011)
    - Having Said to Ed Dorn that the Word as Thing... Photocopy. 1p., March 9, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1012)
    - So that all is an Lord in the Stream... Photocopy. 1p., March 15, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1013)
    - The Portion. Typescript. 2p., April 17 and May 24, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1014)
    - Of Certain Flies. Manuscript. 1p., May 3, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1015)
    - Over the hill and by the shiny water... Manuscript. 2p., May 3, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1016)
    - Carried you the Handsome Harbor... Photocopy. 1p., ca. July 6, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1017)
    - Be careful Kelly You are bright... Typescript. 1p., ca. October 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1018)
    - The name, on a ship tied up at Fulton Street slip... Typescript. 3p. Annotated., October 8, 1960. (Box 22, Folder 1019)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 23)
    - Conrad and B. Ellery. Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1961-1962. (Box 23, Folder 1020)
    - The Limenburg Poem. Manuscript. 8p., ca. 1961-1962. (Box 23, Folder 1021)
    - The Zouche Phoenix, for example... Typescript. 3p., ca. 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1022)
    - Thoughts on the Occasion of St. Valentine's Day... Typescript. 1p., February 18, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1023)
    - The Science of Mythology. Typescript. 1p., February 28, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1024)
    - The charm of perfect land... Manuscript. 1p., ca. March 15, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1025)
    - My love poem for you on St. Joseph's Day. Manuscript. 1p., March 19, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1026)
    - From the Cunt the Anodos... Fragments. 1p., May 7, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1027)
    - I went to sea the first time... Manuscript. 1p., ca. May 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1028)
    - As powerful as the rose... Manuscript. 4p., May 19, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1029)
    - June 30th, 1961. Manuscript. 3p., June 30, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1030)
    - Scoptophilia: look on her, and weep... Typescript. 1p., ca. July 9, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1031)
    - The whole genetic stream is a ribbon... Typescript. 1p., ca. July 9, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1032)
    - Moon over Castine, Moon over Gloucester, 1961. Manuscript. 40p., ca. July 9, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1033)
    - Holding a book up to the city... Typescript. 1p., ca. July 9, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1034)
    - We live in a beast society... Manuscript. 1p., ca. September 10, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1035)
    - Thou thoughtest to escape the gods' notice... Manuscript. 1p., ca. September 11, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1036)
    - Saturn and Jupiter are my planets... Typescript. 2p., September 20, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1037)
    - Naming. Manuscript. 1p., October 18, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1038)
    - Similitude. Typescript. 1p., December 12, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1039)
    - A New Calendar. Typescript. 1p., December 12, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1040)
    - Fragment of Translation and Comment. Typescript. 2p., December 12, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1041)
    - In Their Hour of Need. Typescript. 1p., December 12, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1042)
    - Something Seen in the Air. Typescript. 1p., December 12, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1043)
    - All That You Do Anyhow. Typescript. 1p., December 3, 1961. (Box 23, Folder 1044)
    - Dream hack into the days of yore... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1961-1962. (Box 23, Folder 1045)
    - The Canal. Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1046)
    - Atlantic Judas-land... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1047)
    - The one where 72nd day the Logos man... Manuscript. 1p., 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1048)
    - As it happened: history... Manuscript. 13p. (Box 23, Folder 1049)
    - The ships came bearing salt from Sicily... Manuscript. 1p., 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1050)
    - In the West the advantage, of the idea and society of millenia... Manuscript. 1p., 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1051)
    - The Motorman... Manuscript. 1p., 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1052)
    - The simply food and clothes... Photocopy. 2p., 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1053)
    - Is what they were talking about, the whole covering of the Earth... Manuscript. 1p., 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1054)
    - Ludovico Gonzaga Asitting in His Chair. Manuscript/Typescript. 10p. (Box 23, Folder 1055)
    - For two years he vacillated... Manuscript. 1p. (Box 23, Folder 1056)
    - Aphrodite's now women with eyes... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., ca. 1962-1963. (Box 23, Folder 1057)
    - 3rd Letter on Georges. Manuscript/Photocopy. 5p., ca. January 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1058)
    - He hid in the women's quarters... Manuscript. 1p., ca. January 8, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1059)
    - At Troezen. Typescript. 2p., January 8-10, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1060)
    - Softly falling snow... Manuscript. 1p., ca. February 14, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1061)
    - Persons are my events... Manuscript. 1p., ca. May 16, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1062)
    - Thatles the Phoenician the water man... Manuscript. 1p., ca. May 16, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1063)
    - June 11, 1962. Manuscript. 1p. (Box 23, Folder 1064)
    - A Man Named Riya, from Minneapolis... Manuscript. 1p., ca. June 12, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1065)
    - Capt. Ralph Parker on the front... Manuscript. 1p., ca. August 31, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1066)
    - Turned the whale to stone... Manuscript. 1p., ca. August 31, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1067)
    - Beau Chapelle the sailing man's manual... Manuscript. 1p., ca. September 21, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1068)
    - Siddhartha Buddha... Manuscript. 1p., ca. October - November 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1069)
    - The lady of Gloucester, our lady of Gloucester... Manuscript. 1p., ca. October - November 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1070)
    - Literally known... Manuscript. 1p., ca. October - November 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1071)
    - I gave her for her whole soul her fervent love... Manuscript. 2p., ca. October - November 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1072)
    - Adam of Bremer and I walked out... Manuscript. 4p., ca. October - November 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1073)
    - The light of the moon strike the moon down... Manuscript. 1p., ca. November 2, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1074)
    - The desire she arms she can satisfy... Manuscript. 2p. (Box 23, Folder 1075)
    - Heat. Manuscript. 1p., ca. October 27, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1076)
    - I've got my pieces of it, Aricia... Manuscript. 1p. Written on letter, dated November 9, 1962, from Cid Corman to Charles Olson., ca. November 9, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1077)
    - I cried in the City... Manuscript. 1p., ca. November 9, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1078)
    - "Fluid" the fluid... Manuscript. 1p., ca. November 15, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1079)
    - Woods, gardens in the woods, roads John Parsons... Photocopy. 1p., ca. November 19, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1080)
    - Atlantid in frost... Photocopy. 5p., ca. November 19, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1081)
    - I had been a sacrament of December... Typescript. 1p., December 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1082)
    - Brang his life after the poem... Manuscript. 2p., December 6, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 1083)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 24)
    - A rope of sand Eternity is... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1963-1964. (Box 24, Folder 1084)
    - The same statement by different speakers... Manuscript. 1p., Fall 1963 - Fall 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1085)
    - The moon was a perfect... Typescript. 1p., ca. 1963-1964. (Box 24, Folder 1086)
    - There should be no oh man... Manuscript. 2p., ca. 1963-1964. (Box 24, Folder 1087)
    - Snow, and star, and light, and sun... Manuscript. 2p., ca. 1963-1965. (Box 24, Folder 1088)
    - Yrs over the curve by the ball-field... Manuscript. 17p., ca. January 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1089)
    - I John Watts sailor nauta... Manuscript. 1p., January 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1090)
    - No motion in sense... Manuscript. 1p., ca. January 15, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1091)
    - Here are arguments if one knows something... Manuscript. 1p., ca. January 15, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1092)
    - The Alembic (for Bel). Manuscript. 5p., ca. January 17-19, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1093)
    - January 22, 1963. Manuscript/Typescript/Photocopy. 11p. (Box 24, Folder 1094)
    - The best soft ice-cream... Manuscript. 2p., January 31, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1095)
    - The 'Scar' of the Flower. Manuscript. 12p., ca. February 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1096)
    - My God - Vitubo? Photocopy. 8p., ca. February - May 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1097)
    - The oldest sound on the earth... Manuscript. 1p., February 5, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1098)
    - Ramp: to eat God's food... Typescript. 1p., ca. Spring 1963 - September 4, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1099)
    - I would persuade you. Manuscript. 9p., ca. March 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1100)
    - The Three Warriors from the Resurrection. Manuscript. 1p., ca. March 26, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1101)
    - Venus is not Love Venus is the Form of Love... Manuscript. 1p., ca. April 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1102)
    - Teucrian gold in Washington... Manuscript. 2p., ca. April 9, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1103)
    - Venus (Heaven's Athena...) Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., ca. April 23, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1104)
    - each One Attends To What He Does... Manuscript. 8p., April 24, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1105)
    - A Sonnet for Michaelangelo. Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., ca. April 27, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1106)
    - Rose red the anaclitic palm... Manuscript. 3p., ca. May 20, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1107)
    - Home - 1st part "party"... Manuscript. 13p., ca. June 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1108)
    - Between Kent Circle and the tennis court... Manuscript. 2p., ca. July 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1109)
    - Earth and sea and Heaven is 9 times around... Typescript. 6p., July 14, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1110)
    - Perceiving she didn't like her twat... Manuscript/Typescript. 6p., ca. Fall 1963 - 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1111)
    - Right along the floor... Typescript. 3p., ca. Fall 1963 - 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1112)
    - On her head she had a red wool hat... Manuscript/Typescript. 13p., ca. October - November 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1113)
    - A tree of time and space... Manuscript. 16p., October 27, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1114)
    - Kitchen Table Poem. Manuscript. 1p., ca. November 8, 1963. (Box 24, Folder 1115)
    - Planted the fruit 2" into the ground... Manuscript/Photocopy. 5p. Fragile., ca. December 1963 - February 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1116)
    - He makes sounds... Manuscript. 1p., December 1963 - March 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1117)
    - Even to the little (Smallmans pricks - the nice). Manuscript/Typescript. 1p., 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1118)
    - The BIO-MORPHIC MUST GO tale quale ipsum est The Apple-Branch (who was my wife. Typescript. 1p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1119)
    - Colors and lyrics carry the City to you... Manuscript. 1p. Fragment., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1120)
    - Cruel, and wicked, and unfair the turn of the year... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1964-1968. (Box 24, Folder 1121)
    - Gulls in the wind on a grey day... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1964-1968. (Box 24, Folder 1122)
    - In the precinct of Gloucester I buried her, the wedding of Venice with the sea, squashy islands my olive Tuscan girl... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1964-1968. (Box 24, Folder 1123)
    - The pounding of her belly the depth (of the sea... Typescript. 1p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1124)
    - Monday: Thursday: Where Nandanandi ever played with the Gopi women... Typescript. 1p., ca. 1964-1966. (Box 24, Folder 1125)
    - My dear Jenny - the intrusion of the metrical form... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1126)
    - The future Lord of Donegal... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., January 1, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1127)
    - Umbo (Boss, or Shield). Manuscript. 2p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1128)
    - Nobody is like God, not even Jesus Christ... Photocopy. 1p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1129)
    - If that damned woman was betraying me with some salesman - a man's honor Frances called it... Manuscript/Typescript. 1p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1130)
    - The Real, and Reason. Or, Formaliter. Typescript. 1p., 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1131)
    - I honestly think the damned ideology is killing you... Manuscript. 1p., ca. 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1132)
    - The River Columbus thought... Manuscript. 1p., 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1133)
    - Where the Sun has fallen... Manuscript. 1p., 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1134)
    - The future Lord of Donegal... Manuscript/Photocopy. 4p., January 1, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1135)
    - An uninterrupted line of extension or continuity. Manuscript. 1p., ca. January - February 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1136)
    - Vivian. Manuscript. 1p., ca. January 4, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1137)
    - They stood them... Manuscript. 1p., ca. January 21, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1138)
    - To be Read in the Pace and Fall as Well as the Accents... Typescript. 1p., January 25, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1139)
    - John Neptune the Indian Shaman... Typescript. 1p., ca. January 25, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1140)
    - Or back into Little River... Manuscript. 1p., ca. February 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1141)
    - Norse battle-axe... Manuscript/Typescript/Photocopy. 4p., February 12, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1142)
    - Dear wife, I beg your forgiveness... Manuscript. 1p., April 10, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1143)
    - To place Bigmans cock... Manuscript/Typescript. 1p., May 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1144)
    - Hell is the psychic complex... Manuscript. 1p., ca. May 6, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1145)
    - The Advantage is All or Love's Side and for Anyone Always. Manuscript. 1p., May 15 and October 19, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1146)
    - Manuscript. Written on "Ace of Pentacles" by John Wieners, New York: Carr and Wilson, 1964., May 15 and October 9, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1147)
    - Time! slow 'advance': condition 'changed'... Manuscript. 17p., June 1, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1148)
    - Make Them Naked Instead. Typescript. 1p., June 6, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1149)
    - Tartaros in Earth before Love... Manuscript. 5p., June 8, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1150)
    - Oh God who makes us partial... Manuscript. 1p., ca. June 10, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1151)
    - Runs with water... Manuscript. 1p., August 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1152)
    - I love man and I love woman... Typescript. 1p., August 11, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1153)
    - Addition, on the Trees of the Fort, August 1964. Manuscript. 1p., August 21, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1154)
    - Complete the cannibalism... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., August 21, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1155)
    - The five years... Typescript. 1p., August 24, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1156)
    - Little Me and his son... Manuscript. 2p., ca. September 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1157)
    - Barbara Whirlwind... Typescript/Photocopy. 3p., September - October 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1158)
    - Far-shining Telephassa... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., September 3, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1159)
    - Roger Babbleson, of Gloucester... Manuscript. 1p., September 19, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1160)
    - Like, Not Get Layed... Typescript. 1p., September 19, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1161)
    - Imbued with the light of heaven... Manuscript. 1p., September 21-22, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1162)
    - Smallmans now dwelling house... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., September 24 - October 3, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1163)
    - All I care to do... Typescript. 1p., October 1, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1164)
    - You better believe in your self... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., October 3, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1165)
    - A city belongs to the biggest businesses... Manuscript. 1p., ca. October 6, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1166)
    - She did not know Evil... Typescript. 1p., October 6, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1167)
    - Going to Bed at Night... Typescript. 1p., October 9, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1168)
    - I went full tilt... Typescript. 1p., October 9, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1169)
    - Her skin covered me... Manuscript/Typescript. 2p., October 9, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1170)
    - Follow Bet into the colors of her dress... Typescript. 1p., October 9, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1171)
    - Kingston the smell of her... Typescript. 1p., ca. October 13, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1172)
    - A Maximus: Kingson, Kingston... Manuscript. 2p., October 14, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1173)
    - Kingson, Kingston. Manuscript. 1p., October 14, 1964. (Box 24, Folder 1174)